autoshopper.com 2016-06-27

# Privacy Statement - AutoShopper.com

**Showcase Publications, Inc.** is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement describes the ways that personally identifiable and anonymous information about our online users is gathered through our website and what we do with that information. The practices described in this policy are applicable to current and former customers and to consumers who do business with us. The policy also explains how we protect the confidentiality and security of our customer information. This Privacy Statement does not apply to any information that You may provide to third parties; for example, other sites linked to Our Website. You should contact such third parties directly to determine their respective privacy policies. By visiting AutoShopper.com, you agree that your visit, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Statement and [Our Terms of Use](http://www.autoshopper.com/termsofuse.asp).

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information We Collect

Anytime you visit AutoShopper.com, we gather certain non-personally identifiable information regarding the means you use to access our site. This information includes the type and version of your browser, your service provider, your IP address and any search engine you may have used to locate the site. We use this information to help diagnose problems with our server, administer the Web site, and compile broad statistical data. In addition, we gather certain navigational information about where you go on our Web sites. This information enables us to determine which areas of the Web sites are most frequently visited and helps us to tailor the sites to the needs and interests of our online visitors. Your IP address may be used to identify possible abuse and may be blocked if abuse is detected. Your information is gathered by us in the aggregate and will not be associated with a specific individual without that individual's consent with the exception of illegal activities. If you engage in any illegal acts while using this Website your IP address will be released to law enforcement agencies. 

## Personally Identifiable Information We Collect

Any information you provide to us (i.e. name, e-mail address, etc.) when you register, place an ad, request information, or use any of the other interactive portions of our Website, is securely maintained on our Web servers and internal systems. This information may be used to provide you with information you've requested about our company, our products and our services, or to provide you with special notices, automotive information, special promotions and other commercial offers that we think may be of interest to you. Though we hope you'll find these communications informative and useful, if you don't, you can always unsubscribe by following the simple instructions included in each email. This data may also be used to tailor your experience on our sites by providing content that is relevant to your interests and geographic region.

By using AutoShopper.com, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.

## Placing An Ad & Registration

Most of the information collected in the registration process will be used to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number, expiration date, money order, wire transfer or check information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. To properly process your credit card information, we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. See the Security section below for more details on security measures and procedures. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties, except those specified in the Sharing section of this policy. 

## Cookies

AutoShopper.com uses cookies to improve your experience with our online content. We keep track of the pages visited by our users by placing a cookie, a small piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive. The cookie contains an ID number that allows us to track the pages you've visited. We aggregate this data with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns. We use this information to improve our site by making it more responsive to the needs of our users. We also use cookies to control the number of times you see advertisements. Cookies don't tell us who you are unless you've specifically given us personally identifiable information. Cookies can't read unrelated data off your hard drive and are not accessible to other sites. Our advertisers and third parties that provide products and/or services through our site may also assign their own cookies, a process we don't control. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings. The help menu on most web browsers contains information on how to set your browser to notify you before accepting a cookie or to disable cookies entirely. However, cookies may be required to complete certain functions on this Website. For example, our search engine, order placement, registration and login won't work properly if you configure your browser not to accept cookies.

## Email Addresses

We require a valid email address for every ad placed on this website. Your email address will be used for buyers to inquire about the vehicle you have for sale. To help protect your email address from spam, your email address will not be displayed online. If you provide us your email address, we may email you about our website or our services, or to inquire about your experience using our website or sites operated by others. From time to time, we'll also send you emails that may include automotive information, special promotions and other commercial offers that we think may be of interest to you. Though we hope you'll find these communications informative and useful, if you don't, you can always unsubscribe by following the simple instructions included in each email. And you can opt-out of receiving these types of commercial offers at all by indicating, when you list a car for sale or inquire about a car listed on our website, that you'd prefer not to receive these communications.

## Links

AutoShopper.com contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Showcase Publications, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by AutoShopper.com.

## Third Party Advertising

Advertisements that appear on AutoShopper.com are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. AutoShopper.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on AutoShopper.com unless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by AutoShopper.com and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

Google AdSense (Google.com)  
If you would like more information about third party advertisements used on this site served from Google.com and to know your choices about not having information used by their advertisers, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Burst Media  
If you would like more information about third party advertisements used on this site served from Burst Media and to know your choices about not having information used by their advertisers, visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

## Sharing

We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, marketing assistance, e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes. 

We may frame or mask another web site so that the look, feel and interface simulate the experience of browsing a genuine AutoShopper.com web page. Extreme care and discretion is exercised when evaluating third party sites. We only brand third party sites if their organization applies stringent security and privacy practices which parallel our own commitment to safe online shopping. 

As our business continues to evolve, we may acquire or sell business units or subsidiaries. Customer information is one of the business assets that would be transferred in these types of transactions. In such a situation, your personally identifiable information would only be used in a manner consistent with our pre-existing Privacy Notice. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

## Your Choices

You are entitled to make certain choices about how we communicate with you. 

  1. You may choose not to provide personal information, even though that might impact your ability to register or receive a particular product or service.
  2. If you do not want to receive marketing email from us, you can follow the unsubscribe link provided in those emails.
  3. If you do not want to receive interest-based advertisements, you can opt out as discussed in the "Third Party Advertising" section above.
  4. You have a number of choices regarding certain Data Technologies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser's setting to decline cookies if you prefer. You may also render some web beacons unusable by rejecting their associated cookies and disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or opting out at Evidon.com or the website of the technology provider. If you choose to decline cookies or similar technologies, however, please note that certain features may not function properly or at all as a result. You may be able to adjust the use of advertising identifiers on mobile devices through the settings on your device. 
  5. If you do not want us to use Location Information, you can decline our initial invitation to provide that information, or opt out by changing the location services settings on your mobile device. However, please note that certain features may not function properly or at all as a result if you opt out.

## Children

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, Showcase Publications, Inc. does not knowingly or intentionally solicit or collect information from minors, and our marketing is not directed to minors. If we determine that a user is under eighteen (18) years of age and has submitted information by way of our website, we will immediately delete such information.

## Surveys

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose any information. Information requested may include demographic information (such as postal code, age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is very important to us. We take steps to keep your information secure at our facilities limiting access only to authorized personnel as needed to perform operations governed by this policy. In addition, when Showcase Publications, Inc. collects credit card information from you, Showcase Publications, Inc. uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption, the industry standard for protecting privacy in web transactions. Please keep in mind that despite these measures, Showcase Publications, Inc. cannot guarantee or warrant 100 percent security of its servers and databases. Moreover, Showcase Publications, Inc. cannot guarantee that personally identifiable information that you submit through the Site will not be intercepted or otherwise disclosed.

## Changes in Our Policy

Showcase Publications, Inc. may amend this Privacy Statement from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Statement, we will post the changes here so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

## Effective Date of this Privacy Statement

This Privacy Statement is effective as of February 1, 2003 and last revised on March 25, 2014.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, you can [contact us](http://www.autoshopper.com/contact/) at:

Showcase Publications, Inc.  
1212 East Main Street  
Lakeland, Florida 33801
